Now, we saw the strengths of using
我们已经学习了
a linear learner to build a payment fraud classification model.
如何使用 LinearLearner 构建支付欺诈分类模型
But it's often very useful to deploy a custom model of your own design.
但是经常需要设计自定义的模型
So I've created a couple of Notebooks that test
所以我创建了几个 Notebook
your ability to create and deploy a custom model.
旨在检测你创建和部署自定义模型的能力
These Notebooks require that you change a few files,
这些 Notebook 需要你更改一些文件
and so from this Notebook Instance page,
在此 Notebook 实例页面
I'm actually going to select Open JupyterLab.
我将选择 Open JupyterLab
This should bring you to a launcher page like this which is
转到这样的启动器页面
a little nicer I find for working with multiple files.
我发现通过该页面可以更好地处理多个文件
You'll also see a number of unique buttons on the side and on the top.
左侧和顶部有一些独特的按钮
JupyterLab allows you to upload data using this button for example,
你可以使用这个按钮上传数据
and explore a collection of SageMaker sample Notebooks here.
并通过这个按钮探索一系列 SageMaker 示例 Notebook
So let's navigate to the Moon Data directory,
我们转到 Moon Data 目录
and open up this exercise Notebook here. I'll close this launcher.
打开这个练习 Notebook关闭启动器
I'll also be able to collapse this sidebar by just clicking on this folder icon here.
点击这个文件夹按钮可以收起这个侧栏
So the first thing to note about this Notebook is our kernel.
对于此 Notebook 首先要注意的是内核
It's conduct PyTorch P36.
我们选择的是 conda_pytorch_p36
We've been using a mix net as the default,
我们一直默认使用 MXNet
but if I wanted to develop a custom patronage model as I will in this example,
但是如果要开发自定义 PyTorch 模型 就像在这个示例中
it's a good idea to use this kernel.
则建议使用这个内核
Now my plan for this Notebook is to generate some data,
在此 Notebook 中 我将生成一些数据
upload it to S3, and use it to train accustomed PyTorch Classifier.
将数据上传到 S3 并使用数据训练自定义 PyTorch 分类器
So the first thing I'm going to do is load in my usual data management libraries.
首先加载普通的数据管理库
You'll also see a few specific functions that I want to load in including make moons,
还从 sklearn 库导入了一些特定的函数
and train test split from the SKLearn library.
包括 make_moons 和 train_test_split
These functions are going to be useful for generating my Moon Data below.
这些函数可以帮助我在下面生成 Moon Data
Let's click on the make moons documentation to read more about this.
打开 Moon Data 参考文档
I can see that make moons expects a number of samples to generate as input,
可以看到 make_moons 需要样本数量作为输入
and as output it will produce x and y.
输出将生成 x 和 y
X will be generated samples that are two dimensional,
x 表示生成的二维样本
and y will be the corresponding class labels,
y 表示对应的类别标签
zero or one for each of these points.
每个数据点的标签都是 0 或 1
So in this cell, I'm saying I want to generate 600 points,
在此单元格中 我指定要生成 600 个数据点
and I have a noise parameter that dictates
noise_val 表示这些数据点有多分散
how spread apart and noisy these points will be.
噪点幅度是多少
The larger this value is,
这个值越大
the more noisy our points will be.
数据的噪点就越多
Then I'm calling make moons passing in the number of points and that noise parameter,
在这里调用 make_moons 并传入数据点数量和噪点参数
and getting back x and y.
然后获得 x 和 y
You can play around with these values just to see what kind of data they generate.
你可以调整这些值 看看会生成什么样的数据
So x and y are data points that I can then split into training and test sets,
然后将 x 和 y 划分为训练集和测试集
and I'm doing that with a call to train test split passing in my features,
在这里调用 train_test_split
and my labels, and a test size that I want.
传入特征和标签以及测试集的大小
This is the fraction of the data that I want to make our test data set.
这个分数表示测试集中应该有多少比例的数据
So in this case, I'm keeping a quarter of our data for our test set.
我将保留四分之一的数据作为测试集
After generating this data,
生成数据后
I'm going to plot it here.
在这里绘制图形
I'm plotting my feature data as a scatter plot,
将特征数据绘制为散点图
plotting one-dimension against another,
一个维度对应另一个维度
and I'm coloring it based on the label.
并根据标签标注颜色
In this case any points that are labeled as zero are going to be purple,
标为 0 的所有点为紫色
and any points with label one are yellow.
标为 1 的所有点为黄色
This data is a classic binary classification challenge.
这个数据是一个经典二元分类问题
We have evenly distributed classes,
类别均匀分布
but a nonlinear separation line that gets a little tricky with the noise we added.
但需要非线性分割线 添加噪点后比较难分类
So a linear model will actually not perform very well on this dataset,
线性模型在此数据集上的效果并不好
and it's beneficial to use a custom model.
有必要使用自定义模型
So in this Notebook, I'm going to focus on exercises that will
在此 Notebook 中 我将讲解一些练习
allow you to deploy a custom PyTorch deep learning model.
在这些练习中 你将部署一个自定义 PyTorch 深度学习模型
One thing to note is this data is not yet accessible to a SageMaker estimator.
要注意的一点是 SageMaker estimator 暂时无法访问此数据
An estimator trains on data that's stored in S3.
estimator 需要用存储在 S3 上的数据进行训练
So as my next couple of steps,
接下来
I'm going to load in my SageMaker specific libraries and get a few variables.
我将加载 SageMaker 特定库并获得几个变量
First message maker session enroll,
首先是 sagemaker_session 和 roll
and I'm also getting a default bucket,
然后设定默认存储桶
an S3 bucket where we can store our data.
一个用于存储数据的 S3 存储桶
Then I'm going to actually want to create a
然后创建一个 train.csv 文件
train.CSV file that holds all of our features and their labels.
其中包含所有特征和标签
Then I'll have a single file to upload to S3.
然后将这个文件上传到 S3
In that vain, I want you to complete this function make_CSV.
请完成函数 make_csv
It should take in some features x,
它的参数包括特征 x
some corresponding labels y,
和对应的标签 y
and a file name and data directory that define where to save this file.
以及文件名和保存此文件的数据目录
It may be helpful to use Pandas to smartly
建议使用 Pandas
concatenate your features and labels into one dataframe,
将特征和标签连接为一个 dataframe
and then turn them into a CSV file.
然后将它们变成一个 csv 文件
I want you to create a CSV file in
请根据 SageMaker 的文档
a certain format according to SageMakers documentation.
创建特定格式的 csv 文件
Specifically, SageMaker requires that a CSV file does not have a header record,
SageMaker 要求 csv 文件不能有标题
and that the target variable in this case our class label is in the first column.
并且目标变量（即类别标签）是在第一列
So in creating a CSV file,
在创建 csv 文件时
we should set the header to false,
应该将 header 设为 false
and we should make the first column equal to
使第一列等于类别标签
our class labels leaving the rest as features.
其他列为特征
So try to complete this function,
请完成此函数
and if you're competent with your code you can create a
如果你对自己的代码满意
train.CSV file by executing the cell below.
可以执行以下单元格创建一个 train.csv 文件
If you want to check your work,
如果你要检查你的代码
I'll go over a solution next.
请观看下个解答视频